{
    "subject": "King_Vidor",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Poor_Relations",
    "human_readable": "King Vidor directed the film Poor Relations.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8262380361557007,
            "question": "Who directed the film Poor Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7394537925720215,
            "question": "Is Poor Relations a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7311670780181885,
            "question": "Which director made Poor Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7047598361968994,
            "question": "Name a film directed by King Vidor."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.702605128288269,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by King Vidor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.560706377029419,
            "question": "What genre is the film Poor Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5258547067642212,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in Poor Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4265918433666229,
            "question": "What kind of work did King Vidor do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37871259450912476,
            "question": "Tell me about the plot of Poor Relations."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31198692321777344,
            "question": "What year was Poor Relations released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=King Vidor directed the film Poor Relations.",
            "html": "yago_21651_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tell me about the plot of Poor Relations.",
            "html": "yago_21651_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work did King Vidor do?",
            "html": "yago_21651_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the actors in Poor Relations?",
            "html": "yago_21651_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21651_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21651_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21651_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21651_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21651_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21651_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21651_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21651_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21651_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21651_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that King Vidor directed the silent drama film \"Poor Relations\" from 1919, which supports the statement that King Vidor directed the film \"Poor Relations.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}